Guide to the Walter Stainton papers, 1914-1983
Stainton, Walter papers, 1914-1983
- Series IV. Theatre Productions
  - International Playbills and Programs
    - Playbills from The Surrey Community Players (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Playbills from Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1955, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Playbills from Various British Theatres, 1927-1968, 1927-1968 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Playbills from Her Majesty's Theatre, 1954/1968, 1954/1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Playbill for Canadian Players, "Hamlet," 1956, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - "Lloyd George Knew My Father" at Savoy Theatre, 1976, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Assorted Theatre Playbills, 1944, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Assorted Playbills, 1954-1957, 1954-1957 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Various Playbills from Stainton's Trip to London, 1955, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Various Playbills from Stainton's Trip to London, 1955, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Various Playbills from Stainton's Trip to London, 1955, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Series V. Theatre Construction
  - Lighting Catalogs
    - "Deluxe Your Theatre" Catalog no.31 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Kliegal Lighting Catalogs, Correspondence, and Pricing, 1926-1960, 1926-1960 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Trumbull "Controlite," February 1929, February 1927 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Display Stage Lighting Co. Catalogs, 1927/1934, 1927/1934 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Ward Leonard Electric Co. Catalogs, including September 1928, September 1928 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Century Lighting Equipment Catalogs and Letters, 1930-1956, 1930-1956 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Ben B. Pablocki and Sons Co. Catalog, late 1940s, Late 1940s (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Capital Stage Lighting Co. Letter (1949) and Catalog (1950), 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Keese Engineering Company Catalog (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - General Electric Lightning Control Switchboards (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - "Overhead Stage Structure Requirements," C.E. Tompkins (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Check List for a School Theatre (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - "Standard Stage Rigging Specifications" (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Assorted Papers on Theatre Construction and Design (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Lighting Articles
    - "Colored Glass for Stage Illumination," H.P. Gage, May 1924, May 1924 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Article on Colored Theatrical Lighting (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - "Lighting the School Auditorium and Stage," by Carl J. Allen: From "Illuminating Engineering," September 1950, September 1950 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - "Television Studio Illumination," by H.M. Gurin and R.L. Zahour: From "Illuminating Engineering," October 1950, October 1950 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "Lighting the School Auditorium and Stage," by Carl J. Allen: From "Illuminating Engineering," March 1951, March 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Lighting Projection Screen Surroundings," by James R. Cravath: From "Illuminating Engineering," June 1951, June 1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "Lighting for the Audience," by Stanley McCandless: From "Illuminating Engineering," August 1951, August 1951 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Current Lighting Practice for Television Production": From "Illuminating Engineering," September 1951, September 1951 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Auditorium Lighting Plan, October 15, 1956, October 15, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "A Testing Ground for Theatre Lighting," March 1938, March 1938 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Various Articles on Theatre Lighting and Specifics (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - "A Testing Ground for Theatre Lighting," from "Electrical West," March 1938, March 1938 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - "A Study of Fluorescent Lamps," by Thomas F.C. Muchmore, 1940, May 4, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - "Architectural Lighting in Theatre Decoration," Francis Hodge, 1947, January 1947 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - "Light Sources and Colored Objects," by Ralph m. Evans, 1949, January 1949 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - "Methods of Illuminating Art Objects and Pictures," by Thomas Smith Kelly, 1949, April 1949 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - "A Little Light on Color," by Julian Ellsworth Garney, 1949, August 1949 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - "bulb Sizes for Incandescent Filament Lamps," by W.E. Anderson, September 1950 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - "Downlighting," by Stanley McCandless, January 1951 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - "Daylight in Classrooms-Multilateral Lighting," by R.L. Biesele, Jr., April 1951 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - "A Demonstration of Electronic Control of Stage Lighting," by George C. Izenour (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Lighting Notes
    - Graphs and Data About Colored Theatrical Lighting (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Articles and Quotes About Lighting (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Problems on Lighting (Notes and Index Cards) (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Inherit the Wind Light Plot (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Lighting Experiments and Laboratory Exercises (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Problems on Lighting (Notes and Index Cards), 1927-1948 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Technical Catalogs and Pamphlets
    - "Little Theatre and Main Auditorium," Submitted by Ward Leonard Electric Co., 1936, April 3, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - "Problems in School Planning," and "Bibliography of Theatre Planning and Equipment" from American Educational Theatre Association Washington Meeting, 1940, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Various Articles on Stage Photography, From "Players Magazine," 1941-1942, December 1941-March 1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - "A Method of Directing Production Photographs," by John Reich (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - "Inexpensive Stage Photography for the Small Theatre," by James H. Miller (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Technical Details of Elmira Little Theatre, 1946, November 1946 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Sealuxe Theatre Display Systems Brochure and Details (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Pevear Color Specialty Company, 1926-1928, 1926-1928 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Wright DeCoster Inc., 1930-1936, 1930-1936 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - International Register Company, K9A Cutawl, 1935-1937, 1935-1937 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - S.O.S. Corp, 1936, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Weber Machine Corporation, March 18, 1938, March 18, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - F. A. Bohling, 1940, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - J. R. Clancy Inc. Theatrical Stage Hardware, November 15, 1940-June 15, 1952, November 15, 1950-June 15, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Thomas J. Valentino Inc, 1941-1953, 1941-1953 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - The Strong Electric Corporation Spotlights, January 11, 1949, January 11, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Theatre Production Services 1951 Price List, May 1954, May 1954 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Wallach and Associates, March 1955, March 1955 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - DeVry Projectors and Accessories (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Kodak Bi-Focal Lens Converter (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Powerlite Switchboard Co. (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Cinetymer Co., 1938, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Modern Lighting Co. (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - NY State Colleges of Agriculture and Home Economics, "Films, Recordings, Slides," September 1952, September 1952 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Controlite Typeboard Schematic, 1936, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - "Detail of Control Panel on Console" for Switchboards, November 7, 1940, November 7, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Architecture Documents for Hampton Institute, 1954, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Architecture Information for Clinton School, Columbus, Ohio; 1955, May 11, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Architecture Information for West Rock Jr. High School, 1955, December 20, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Various Architecture Documents for Little Theater at University of Connecticut, 1955-1956, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - General Radio Company Brochure, 1948, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Assorted Schematics and Theatre Details (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Construction and Design Articles
    - "Designing the Community Center Type of Theatre," September 26, 1931, September 26, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - "Basic Theater Planning," by Lee Simonson, from "Architectural Forum," September 1932, September 1932 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - "The School Auditorium as a Theater," by Alice Barrows and Lee Simonson, 1939, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - "Planning and Equipping the Educational Theatre," by A.S. Gillette, 1945, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - "Are You Going to Build a Theatre?" on Plans and Architecture, from National Theatre Conference 1947, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Article on Theatre Architecture by Arch Lauterer (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Booklets and Articles on School Theatres and Auditoriums (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Bibliographies of Theatre Planning and Equipment from American Educational Theatre Association (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - "Theatre Architecture: A Brief Bibliography" by Frederick Arden Pawley, 1932, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - "Architecture for the New Theatre," by Arthur Loomis Hamon, February 1936, February 1936 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - "Theatrical Stage Craft: Ancient and Modern," by J.R. Vincent (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - "Typical Stage Interior" by J.R. Clancy, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Assorted Notes on Theatre Specifications (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Assorted Articles on Proper Theatre Protocols (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Articles on Perspective and Drawing in Theatre (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Papers on Theatre Architecture and Planning (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Assorted Papers and Articles on Theatre Planning (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - "Auditorium," Architectural Forum, January 1935, January 1935 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - "Architecture for the New Theatre," by Arthur Loomis Hamon, February 1936, February 1936 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Assorted Papers Concerning Theatre Buildings, 1941-1954 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - "The Shorewood High School Auditorium: Ann Application of Modern Concepts and Practices in Auditorium Design," 1949, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Papers on Theatre and Stage Construction (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Acoustics and Sound Articles
    - Starr Piano Co. "Speedy-Q" Sound Effects, January 15, 1937, January 15, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Gennett Electrical Transcription and Sound Effects, 1937-1938, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Standard Radio Sound Effects (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Charles Michelson Inc. Sound Effects Records, March 1951, March 1951 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Articles and Magazines on Acoutstics, 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Articles and Papers on Sound (Theatrical/Cinematic) (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Technical Photos
    - Switchboard (prints) from Trumbill Electric, Dartmouth 1928, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Photo Negatives, November 1947, November 27, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Documents/Photos from University of Alabama Theatre, 1947-1948, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Stroposcopic Disk for Phono Turntable-Photo (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Switchboard, Severance Hall (Prints) (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Switchboard at Montana State University (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Photos of South Western Theatres (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Various Prints of Lightning Equipment (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Unidentified Photo Negative (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Syracuse Museum of Fine Arts Playhouse Photos (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Contact Prints from 35mm, 1939, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Sound Recording, W.S. Theatre, Prints/Negative, December 1940, December 1940 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Pictures of New Switchboards, 1948, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Motion Picture in Our Society, Library Lobby Exhibition at Festival of Contemporary Arts, April 1953, April 1953 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Photos of Stage Laboratory in Morse Hall, February 1955, February 1955 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Theatre Sound Equipment, Prints (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Photos for Rand Laboratory, 1955-1962, 1955-1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Assorted Theatre Photos, 1939, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Thunder Rock Production Shots, Negatives and Prints, 1942, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Comfort Zone Chart, Prints (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Kermis Sets, Drawings and Diagrams (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - "Right You Are! (If You Think So) Prints, from Dartmouth (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "Olympia," Negatives and Prints (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - "Twelfth Night,' Chekhow Theatre Studio Production Shots (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Windows (Prints) (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Series VI. Cornell University Campus
  - General Campus
    - "A Site for an Arena Theatre on Central Campus," by Sidney Freeman, August 1950, August 1950 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - "Suggestions for New Buildings Requested for the Department of Speech and Dramatics," May 1927, May 1927 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Minute About Cornell Centennial Celebration, 1965, March-June 1965 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Newspaper Articles About Cornell Centennial Celebration, 1965, June 1965 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - "Cornell in Sound and Light," Centennial Celebration Script, 1965, June 20, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence About Bailey Hall Safety Hazards, 1940, February-October 1940 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Newspaper Articles Concerning Changes to Cornell Campus and Various Recollections (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Papers About Cornell Theatre Buildings, 1930-1954, 1930-1954 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Papers on Barnes Hall, December 6, 1946-October 17, 1947, December 6, 1946 - October 17, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Willard Straight Hall/Theatre
    - Correspondence Concerning Willard Straight Hall (Films, Dramatic Club, etc.), 1928-1937, 1928-1937 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - "Sinbad the Sailor" Dramatic Club Playbill and Ad., November 17, 1932, November 17, 2132 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Receipts for Film Showings, August 12, 1937-April 1, 1943, August 12, 1937-April 1, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence Concerning Willard Straight Hall (Films, Dramatic Club, etc.), 1938-1945, 1938-1945 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Misc. Documents Concerning Willard Straight Hall (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Floor Plans for Proposed Additions to Willard Straight Hall, April 30, 1948, April 30, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Articles About Willard Straight Theatre Dealing with History and Improvements, 1947, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - List of Films Shown at Willard Straight Theatre, 1944-1952, 1944-1952 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Layout of Willard Straight Hall, 1925, November 18, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Article, "Willard Straight Gift Enriches Cornell Life," 1945, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Papers About Willard Straight Hall University Theatre (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Article About Murals in Willard Straight Theatre (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Willard Straight Hall, Cornell University," 1925, November 18, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Photos and Layouts of Willard Straight Theatre (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Statler Hall
    - Correspondence About Improving Alice Statler Auditorium, 1955-1956, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence About Improving Alice Statler Auditorium, 1957-1964, 1957-1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Alice Statler Auditorium: Stage Lighting Circuiting and Equipment Revisions, April 3, 1957, April 3, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Pictures of Electrical Equipment for Alice Statler Auditorium (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Notes About Improvement of Alice Statler Auditorium (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Notes About Improving Alice Statler Auditorium (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Alice Statler Auditorium Lighting Control System Schematics (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Article About Alice Statler Memorial Auditorium (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Theatre Specifications for Alice Statler Auditorium (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Lighting Suggestions for Alice Statler Auditorium (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - "Memorandum on Statler Auditorium Lighting," 1956, July 31, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence with Frank Rhodes Concerning Alice Statler Auditorium, April 1979assorted, April 4, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Series VII. Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Books and Documents from Past Plays
    - Script for Thurber and Nugent's "The Male Animal," 1941, 194 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - "The Second Sheperd's Play" Script and Staging, 1948, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - "Macbeth" Script and Staging, 1949, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Prompt Book for Cornell Dramatic Club Performance of "The Bucktails," Volume 1 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Prompt Book for Cornell Dramatic Club Performance of "The Bucktails," Volume 2 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - "She Stoops to Conquer, Or, The Mistakes of a Night" by Oliver Goldsmith: Script, Notes, Staging, 1936, May 8, 1936 (Box 6)
    - "Charley's Aunt" by Brandon Thomas: Script, Notes, Staging, 1937, February 12-13, 1937 (Box 6)
    - "What a Life" by Clifford Goldsmith: Script, Notes, Staging, 1940, August 2-3, 1940 (Box 6)
    - "Thunder Rock" by Robert Ardrey: Script, Notes, Staging, 1942, April 17-18, 1942 (Box 6)
    - "The Damask Cheek" by John van Druten and Lloyd Morris: Script, Notes, Staging, 1946, November 20-23, 1946 (Box 6)
    - "Blithe Spirit" by Noel Coward: Script, Notes, Staging, 1948, February 6-7, 1948 (Box 6)
    - "Night Must Fall" by Emlyn Williams: Script, Notes, Staging, 1948, May 21-22, 1948 (Box 6)
    - "George and Margaret" by Gerald Savory: Script, Notes, Staging (Box 6)
    - "Right You Are (If You Think So)" by Luigi Pirandello: Script, Notes, Staging (Box 6)
    - "Double Demon" by Luigi Pirandello: Script, Notes, Staging (Box 6)
    - "The Second Man" by S. N. Behrman: Script, Notes, Staging (Box 6)
    - "Deep are the Roots" by Arnaud D'Usseau and James Gow: Script, Notes, Staging (Box 6)
    - "Two Blind Mice" by Samuel Spewack: Script, Notes, Staging (Box 6)
    - Reproduced Flyers for Plays from 1756-1798, 1759-1798; These plays, some evolved from "The Country Wife," are: "The Rival Queens, or The Death of Alexander the Great;" "The Country Girl;" "Jealous Wife;" "Joan of Arc, or the Maid of Orleans.' (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Reviews for "The Country Wife," 1935-1936, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Wycherley's "The Country Wife," September 1935, September 1935 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence between Stainton, Ashley Dukes, and Gilbert Miller About Cornell's Performance of "The Country Wife," September 1953, September 1953 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Partial Script for "The Country Wife" (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Personal Notes on "The Country Wife" (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Photos from Unknown Production of "The Country Wife" (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Possible Music from "The Country Wife:" Records from Recordisc Corp.: "Overture," and "Suite in E Minor" (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Cast List/Production Details for "Romeo and Juliet" (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Script and Production Details for "Man of Destiny" (Box 15)
    - Script and Production Details for "Man of Destiny" (Box 15)
    - Script and Production Details for "The Drunkard: or, The Fallen Saved" (Box 15)
    - Script and Production Details for "The Dover Road" (Box 15)
    - Script and Production Details for "Ten Nights in a Bar-Room" (Box 15)
    - Papers from "Ten Nights in a Bar-Room" (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Papers from "The Fire of Vests" (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Script and Production Details for "Seven Keys to Baldpate," 1927, 1927 (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Fanny's First Play," 1930, 1930 (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Under the Gaslight" (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Ah, Wilderness!" (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "The Far-Off Hills" (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Excursion" (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Ten Nights in a Bar-Room, 1952", 1952 (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Ten Nights in a Bar-Room," 1952, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Script for "Clear All Wires!", There are two of these scripts. (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "The Star-Wagon" (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "The Donovan Affair" (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Holiday: A Comedy in Three Acts" (Box 16)
    - Script and Production Details for "Major Barbara, 1931", 1931 (Box 16)
  - Playbills
    - Playbills and Notes Concerning Cornell's Production of "The Male Animal," 1941, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Playbill for "Pyramus and Thisbe from A Midsummer Night's Dream," 1949, September 18, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Playbills and Statistics for Dramatic Club Productions, 1947-1950, 1947-1950; Contains playbills for: "Joan of Lorraine," 1947; "Alison's House," 1947; "The Second Shepherd's Play," 1947; An Evening of One Act Plays, 1947: "Ile" (O'Neill), "A Seat in the Park" (Pinero), "Lord Byron's Love Letter" (Williams), "The Happy Journey" (Wilder);"In the Suds," 1947; "On Approval", 1948; "The Tatterman Marionettes," 1948; "Blithe Spirit," 1948; "The Doctor in Spite of Himself," 1948; "The Philadelphia Story," 1948; "The Red Gate Players," 1948; "Two Blind Mice," 1950 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1914-1921, 1914-1921 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills, 1919-1948, 1919-1948 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Playbills from Cornell Women's Dramatic Club, 1920s, 1920s (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills, 1920-1021, 1920-1921 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills, 1920-1926, 1920-1926 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1921-1923, 1921-1923 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Playbills and Summary from Cornell Dramatic Club's Seasons, 1921-1923, 1921-1923 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, May 1924 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club Performances, October-December 1925, October-December 1925 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1940, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1943, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1944-1945, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Playbills for Cornell Dramatic Club, 1945-1946, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club Performances, 1947, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, September-December 1948, September-December 1948 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1949-1950, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club Productions, mid 1950s, mid 1950s (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1952-1963, 1952-1963 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Playbills from Cornell Dramatic Club, 1953, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Playbills for Cornell Dramatic Club, June-December 1956, June-December 1956 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Flyer for Cornell Dramatic Club Production, "Ten Nights in a Bar-Room (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Playbills for Cornell Dramatic Club, 1926, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Playbills for Cornell Dramatic Club, 1926-1928, 1926-1928 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Playbills for Cornell Dramatic Club, 1929-1930, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Playbills for Cornell Dramatic Club, 1932-1935, 1932-1935 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Playbills for Cornell Dramatic Club, 1936-1938, 1936-1938 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills, 1943-1944, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills, 1939, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills, 1950-1951, 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills and Assorted Papers, 1950-1952, 1950-1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Playbills, 1952-1953, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Administration Documents
    - List of Dramatic Club Presidents, 1909-1947, 1909-1947 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - List of Cornell Dramatic Club Presidents, 1920-1947 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Cornell Dramatic Club Officer List, 1946-1948, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - List of Dramatic Club Presidents, 1909-1947, 1 (Box 7, Folder 52)